* Alaska Travel Specials
        
        * Image

    * Alaska Travel Specials
        
        * Image

    * Alaska Travel Specials
        
        * Image

    * Alaska Travel Specials
        
        * Image

    Can we help you discover Alaska?
    
    Search 

Can we help you discover Alaska?

Search 

Close Search

Image

Photo Credit: ATIA, Michael DeYoung

X

Privacy Policy
==============

Privacy Policy

------------------

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which the Alaska Travel Industry Association (“ATIA”) compiles, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the TravelAlaska.com website ("Site"). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and all associated products and services offered by the State of Alaska. Our Privacy Policy is shared with you because we respect your right to online privacy and are committed to protecting your privacy while using our Site.

**Personal identification information**  
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, register on the Site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and credit card information, as applicable. We may work with data providers to serve advertising to you through display media or other methods. These providers may use personal information that we have collected or that you have provided to locate you online, such as when you visit our Site. This information may be linked to online identifiers or IP addresses assigned to you, and to demographic or interest-based data, in order to target you with relevant advertising, including advertising about products or services offered by us or our industry partners. To learn more about or opt out of this and other interest-based advertising, please visit the industry opt-out pages operated by the DAA, at [http://www.aboutads.info](https://protect-us.mimecast.com/s/IkQpCL9pxDHqJYfBSe5f?domain=aboutads.info) and by the NAI at [http://networkadvertising.org](https://protect-us.mimecast.com/s/DOviCM8qyguPQ6IkWPg2?domain=networkadvertising.org).

**Non-personal identification information**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

**Web browser cookies**  
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**  
ATIA may collect and use Users’ personal information for the following purposes:

* To improve customer service - information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.
* To personalize user experience - we may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.
* To improve our Site and advertising - we may use feedback you provide to third-parties such as Arrivalist Technology and other organizations to determine the effectiveness of TravelAlaska.com and the advertising performed by ATIA. 
* To process payments - we may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service.
* To share your information with third parties - we may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.
* To run a promotion, contest, survey, or other Site feature.
* To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.
* To send periodic emails to Users with information and updates pertaining to their order and respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. Users may also receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time a User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
* To evaluate the effectiveness of TravelAlaska.com

**How we protect your information**  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices, and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information, and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users occurs over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures. Our Site is also in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users.

**Sharing your personal information**  
We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site and administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission.

When Users request information, the option to receive additional information is presented. If you opt-in by providing your address and/or email address this information may be made available to site advertisers through a Mailing Label or E-mail Leads program. All emails distributed through the Email Leads program will be sent by the ATIA, or an authorized agent. Your email address will never be distributed directly to a third party for re-use.

**Online advertising we use**  
We use multiple online advertising platforms to advertise TravelAlaska.com across the Internet. These services will capture basic non-personal information about your visit to our site as well as some personal information, such as your IP address, to display relevant ads tailored to you based on your visit to TravelAlaska.com by placing a cookie on your machine. These services allow us to tailor our marketing to better suit your needs and only display ads that are relevant to you.

**Third party websites**  
Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**Third party services**  
We use third party services such as Google, Microsoft, Arrivalist Technology, and other services that collect user information through various means while viewing our Site and online advertisements. The policies regarding the use and protection of this data is defined by these organizations and is not the responsibility of the ATIA.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
ATIA has the discretion to update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. By accessing the Site, you acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**  
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact us at:

Alaska Travel Industry Association  
610 E. 5th Ave., Ste. 200,   
Anchorage, AK 99501

This document was last updated on March 20, 2024

Share

Copy Link 

### 

Alaska: AKA Your Next Adventure

Where will your Alaska adventure take you? Order our Official State of Alaska Vacation Planner and plot your course.

#### Stay Connected with the Travel Alaska Newsletter

Monthly travel tips, highlights, and savings! View past newsletters [here](https://www.travelalaska.com/travel-alaska-newsletter).

Your Email 

Your County

Country Your CountryAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua & BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAscension IslandAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia & HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBritish Virgin IslandsBruneiBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCanary IslandsCape VerdeCaribbean NetherlandsCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicCeuta & MelillaChadChileChinaChristmas IslandClipperton IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongo - BrazzavilleCongo - KinshasaCook IslandsCosta RicaCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzechiaCôte d’IvoireDenmarkDiego GarciaDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatiniEthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard & McDonald IslandsHondurasHong Kong SAR ChinaHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKosovoKuwaitKyrgyzstanLaosLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacao SAR ChinaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmar (Burma)NamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorth KoreaNorth MacedoniaNorwayOmanOutlying OceaniaPakistanPalauPalestinian TerritoriesPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairn IslandsPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRomaniaRussiaRwandaRéunionSamoaSan MarinoSarkSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia & South Sandwich IslandsSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSt. BarthélemySt. HelenaSt. Kitts & NevisSt. LuciaSt. MartinSt. Pierre & MiquelonSt. Vincent & GrenadinesSudanSurinameSvalbard & Jan MayenSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaSão Tomé & PríncipeTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad & TobagoTristan da CunhaTunisiaTurkmenistanTurks & Caicos IslandsTuvaluTürkiyeU.S. Outlying IslandsU.S. Virgin IslandsUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVatican CityVenezuelaVietnamWallis & FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabweÅland Islands

 I understand that by clicking submit I am agreeing to Travel Alaska's [Privacy Policy](https://www.travelalaska.com/Privacy-Policy). View [GDPR FAQs](https://www.travelalaska.com/gdpr). \*

Leave this field blank 

##### Stay Connected

OFFICIAL STATE OF ALASKA VACATION AND TRAVEL INFORMATION

Copyright 2024 Alaska Travel Industry Association

Travel Alaska is a registered trademark of Alaska Travel Industry Association.
